Software Developer

Arthur Henry

Professional Summary

As a software developer, I offer a wide variety of experiences and challenges from project-to-project. I provide best business practices for the design, development, and execution of software solutions. Specialize in cloud infrastructure, full-stack development, and agile methodologies.

Experience

Software Developer - ELPHA, San Francisco, CA

August 2021 - Present

- Created YAML template files for AWS CloudFormation to manage infrastructure such as API Gateway, Lambda functions, DynamoDB tables, S3 buckets, Athena databases, and users.
- Collaborated with cross-functional teams to streamline cloud-based workflows and processes, optimizing efficiency.
- Supported management and maintenance of cloud infrastructure to ensure stability, scalability, and security.
- Managed policies, access controls, and security configurations in AWS and other cloud environments.

Full Stack Developer - Hewlett Packard, Phoenix, AZ

June 2017 - August 2021

- Designed and implemented web applications using both front-end and back-end technologies.
- Developed Single Page Applications (SPAs) with React for login pages, main pages, and integration setups.
- Created a customer resolution management tool using React and Java, improving customer support efficiency.
- Worked with payment teams to enhance user experience for over 50,000 customers, saving time and improving cash flow.

System Administrator - Sprint-Paranet, Chicago, IL

March 2013 – June 2017

- Oversaw and maintained IT infrastructure, ensuring systems were secure, reliable, and up-to-date.
- · Configured, optimized, and automated server and network performance.
- Provided technical support, troubleshooting, and debugging for software systems.
- Collaborated with teams to develop business solutions to increase profits through agile methodologies.

Projects

Project 1 - Cloud Automation Tool

Built an automated tool to streamline cloud deployment processes using AWS services, improving deployment efficiency by 30%.

Project 2 - Customer Resolution Management System

Developed a customer resolution management system using React and Java, improving customer support efficiency by 20%.

3 520-709-1298

art_a_henry@yahoo.com

https://arthur-online-resume

Education

Keller Graduate School of Management

Master's in Computer Information Systems (June 2016 – August 2018)

DeVry University

Bachelor's in Computer Science (March 2011 – June 2015)

| Skills | |
|------------|------|
| JavaScript | **** |
| Java | **** |
| React | **** |
| Kubernetes | **** |
| NodeJS | **** |
| Python | **** |
| AWS | **** |
| Docker | **** |
| Git | **** |
| Linux | **** |